{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Closet \u0026 Storage Organizers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40429/":{"taskOID":40429,"originalTaskOID":40429,"setID":1010,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6918,"questionDisplayText":"Area(s) to Organize","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the closet or room where this organizer system will be installed: (Select all that apply) ","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10075,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walk in closet","answerDisplayText":"Walk in closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10076,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Media room","answerDisplayText":"Media room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10077,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reach in closet","answerDisplayText":"Reach in closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10078,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10079,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10080,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10081,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen/Pantry","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen/Pantry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10082,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6919,"questionDisplayText":"Storage Materials Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of organization are you hoping to install? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10083,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drawers","answerDisplayText":"Drawers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Baskets","answerDisplayText":"Baskets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10087,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hanging storage","answerDisplayText":"Hanging storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6918,"questionDisplayText":"Area(s) to Organize","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the closet or room where this organizer system will be installed: (Select all that apply) ","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10075,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walk in closet","answerDisplayText":"Walk in closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10076,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Media room","answerDisplayText":"Media room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10077,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reach in closet","answerDisplayText":"Reach in closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10078,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10079,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10080,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10081,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen/Pantry","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen/Pantry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10082,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10075,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walk in closet","answerDisplayText":"Walk in closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10076,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Media room","answerDisplayText":"Media room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10077,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Reach in closet","answerDisplayText":"Reach in closet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10078,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home office","answerDisplayText":"Home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10079,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10080,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10081,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen/Pantry","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen/Pantry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10082,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6919,"questionDisplayText":"Storage Materials Desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of organization are you hoping to install? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10083,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drawers","answerDisplayText":"Drawers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Baskets","answerDisplayText":"Baskets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10087,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hanging storage","answerDisplayText":"Hanging storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10083,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shelving","answerDisplayText":"Shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10084,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drawers","answerDisplayText":"Drawers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Baskets","answerDisplayText":"Baskets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10086,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10087,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hanging storage","answerDisplayText":"Hanging storage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10088,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40429/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40429,"taskName":"Room or Closet Organizers - Install","taskDescription":"Install Room or Closet Organizer","xmTaskDescriptor":"Closet \u0026 Storage Organizers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1210,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Closet california organization improvement addition cabinets","textMessagingName":"Organize Closet","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms specialize in planning \u0026 installing customized systems of racks, shelves \u0026 bins to bring order \u0026 expand the storage capacity of closets, garages, pantries, offices \u0026 similar areas.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes products, systems and advice for organizing closets \u0026 rooms","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install Room or Closet Organizers.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Professional Closet Organizers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Room \u0026 Storage Organization","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":14,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Room or Closet Organizer Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Room or Closet Organizer - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Organizer Need","urlName":"Closets-or-Rooms-Organize","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Closet Organizers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Closet,california,organize, shelf, shelves, cabinets, walk-in, walk, in, bookshelfs, book, bookshelves","emcCategoryOid":-12052,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1010,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}